Inventory of the Alexandra Andreevna Voronine Yourieff Papers
Hoover Institution Archives
- W. George Yourieff--Diploma, American Institute of Architects, 1962
- Three framed watercolor images on Chinese motifs, undated
- Color photocopy of Chinese city of Tsingtao, and Yourieff's family house there, undated
- Framed watercolor painting by W. George Yourieff, Tsingtao, China, undated (Box 80)
- W. George Yourieff
  - Certificate, California State Board of Architectural Examiners, 1986.
    Framed image
  - Certificate, building designer, State of California, 1966 September.
- Notice, French Consulate, Tsingtao, China, 1940s(?)
- Alexandra Yourieff--Advertisement of her exhibit at the Palo Alto Art Club, California, undated.
- 2 albums depicting family and friends, undated (Box 81)
- W. George Yourieff--Business accounting book, 1970-1975
- One oversize framed photograph depicting two images of W. George Yourieff, undated (Box 82)
- Writings--Quisling book. In Quisling's Shadow: The Memoirs of Vidkun Quisling's First Wife Alexandra, by Alexandra Andreevna Voronine Yourieff with George Yourieff and Kirsten A. Seaver, undated (Box-folder 83: 1)
- Correspondence, 1983. (Folder 83: 2)
  Includes brochure of memoirs and essays on Vladimir Maiakovskii. In Swedish
- Writings--Quisling book. Copies of Alle Kvinner magazine, Oslo, Norway, 1975, and article on Vidkun Quisling written by Kirsten A. Seaver, Aftenposten, Norway, 1992 March 10 (Folder 83: 3-4)
- Motion picture film
  - Untitled 8mm film (Film shelf Film shelf)